Guide to the National Education Association-Special Collections records, 1857-2015 NEA1007.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Projects, 1953-2000; Series 8; 90 Linear Feet
  - Project 18-Maryland [2/2], 1969-1971; Series 8 (Box 2706, Folder 20)
    Written on folder: General SNEA Correspondence Student MSTA Conference Material GRIP-Maryland Meeting Teach-In Correspondence Failure Vote 18 Bill SPAN Correspondence Voter Registration Maryland Effort
  - Project 18-Massachusetts [1/2], 1969-1970; Series 8 (Box 2706, Folder 21)
    Written on folder: SNEA Correspondence Vote 18 Issue Correspondence Polls Vote 18 Teach-In Referendum Campaign
  - Project 18-Massachusetts [2/2], 1969-1970; Series 8 (Box 2706, Folder 22)
  - Project 18-Michigan [1/2], 1966-1970; Series 8 (Box 2706, Folder 23)
  - Project 18-Michigan [2/2], 1970-1971; Series 8 (Box 2707, Folder 1)
  - Project 18-Minnesota, 1969-1970; Series 8 (Box 2707, Folder 2)
  - Project 18-Minnesota Youth Franchise Coalition, 1971; Series 8 (Box 2707, Folder 3)
  - Project 18-Miscellaneous [file 1/2], 1970; Series 8 (Box 2707, Folder 4)
  - Project 18-Miscellaneous [file 2/2], 1969-1970; Series 8 (Box 2707, Folder 5)
  - Project 18-Missouri, 1969-1970; Series 8 (Box 2707, Folder 6)
  - Project 18-Missouri-SNEA Correspondence, Ratification Correspondence, 1969-1971; Series 8 (Box 2707, Folder 7)
  - Project 18-Mississippi, 1969-1970; Series 8 (Box 2707, Folder 8)
  - Project 18-Mississippi, 1969-1970; Series 8 (Box 2707, Folder 9)
  - Project 18-Montana, 1969-1970; Series 8 (Box 2707, Folder 10)
  - Project 18-Montana-SNEA Correspondence, Montana Referendum Correspondence, Teach-In Correspondence, 1969-1971; Series 8 (Box 2707, Folder 11)
  - Project 18-NASSP and NASC (Vote-18), 1969-1970; Series 8 (Box 2707, Folder 12)
  - Project 18-NCSS-National Council for the Social Studies, 1969-1970; Series 8 (Box 2708, Folder 1)
  - Project 18-NCTEPS, 1969-1970; Series 8 (Box 2708, Folder 2)
  - Project 18-NEA 26th Amendment Correspondence, 1971; Series 8 (Box 2708, Folder 3)
  - Project 18-NEA Ratification Effort, 1971; Series 8 (Box 2708, Folder 4)
  - Project 18-NEA Regional Offices, 1970; Series 8 (Box 2708, Folder 5)
  - Project 18-NEA Support VRA, 1970; Series 8 (Box 2708, Folder 6)
  - Project 18-NEA Units, 1969-1970; Series 8 (Box 2708, Folder 7)
  - Project 18-Nebraska, 1968-1970; Series 8 (Box 2708, Folder 8)
  - Project 18-Nebraska-Referendum Effort, Referendum Election Night Contacts, 1968-1970; Series 8 (Box 2708, Folder 9)
  - Project 18-New Hampshire, 1968-1970; Series 8 (Box 2708, Folder 10)
  - Project 18-New Hampshire-General Issue Information, mini SPAN, Ratification Effort, SNEA-NH Coverage, 1970-1971; Series 8 (Box 2708, Folder 11)
  - Project 18-New Jersey-Referendum, Correspondence, U.R. Quest, 1969-1970; Series 8 (Box 2708, Folder 12)
  - Project 18-New Jersey II, 1969-1971; Series 8 (Box 2708, Folder 13)
  - Project 18-New Mexico, 1969-1970; Series 8 (Box 2709, Folder 1)
  - Project 18-New Mexico-Correspondence, 1968-1971; Series 8 (Box 2709, Folder 2)
  - Project 18-Newsletter, News Mailings, 1969; Series 8 (Box 2709, Folder 3)
  - Project 18-New York, 1969-1970; Series 8 (Box 2709, Folder 4)
  - Project 18-Nevada, 1969; Series 8 (Box 2709, Folder 5)
  - Project 18-New York-Correspondence, 1969-1971; Series 8 (Box 2709, Folder 6)
  - Project 18-Nevada-Ratification Correspondence, 1969-1971; Series 8 (Box 2709, Folder 7)
  - Project 18-North Carolina, 1969-1971; Series 8 (Box 2709, Folder 8)
  - Project 18-North Dakota, 1969-1970; Series 8 (Box 2709, Folder 9)
  - Project 18-North Dakota-Correspondence, 1968; Series 8 (Box 2709, Folder 10)
  - Project 18-Ohio, 1970-1971; Series 8 (Box 2709, Folder 11)
  - Project 18-Ohio-Campaign, 1969; Series 8 (Box 2709, Folder 12)
  - Project 18-Oklahoma, 1969-1970; Series 8 (Box 2709, Folder 13)
  - Project 18-Oklahoma-Correspondence, 1969-1971; Series 8 (Box 2709, Folder 14)
  - Project 18-Oregon, 1969; Series 8 (Box 2709, Folder 15)
  - Project 18-Oregon-Correspondence, 1969-1970; Series 8 (Box 2709, Folder 16)
  - Project 18-Organizations-AFL-CIO, 1969; Series 8 (Box 2710, Folder 1)
  - Project 18-Pennsylvania, 1969-1971; Series 8 (Box 2710, Folder 2)
  - Project 18-Pennsylvania-Correspondence, 1969; Series 8 (Box 2710, Folder 3)
  - Project 18-Photos, ca. 1968-1971; Series 8 (Box 2710, Folder 4)
    Contains 73 photographs.
  - Project 18-Pictures Launching 18 Vote, 1969; Series 8 (Box 2710, Folder 5)
  - Project 18-Publicity (NEA) P/S, 1970; Series 8 (Box 2710, Folder 6)
  - Project 18-Puerto Rico-Referendum Press Coverage, 1970; Series 8 (Box 2710, Folder 7)
  - Project 18-Ratification Survey and Report, 1971 February 11; Series 8 (Box 2710, Folder 8)
  - Project 18-Resumes, ca. 1969; Series 8 (Box 2710, Folder 9)
  - Project 18-Rhode Island, 1969; Series 8 (Box 2710, Folder 10)
  - Project 18-Rhode Island-General Issue Correspondence, 1970; Series 8 (Box 2710, Folder 11)
  - Project 18-Social Studies Survey Questionnaire-Responses, Results, 1969; Series 8 (Box 2710, Folder 12)
  - Project 18-South Carolina, 1970; Series 8 (Box 2710, Folder 13)
  - Project 18-South Carolina-Correspondence, 1969-1970; Series 8 (Box 2710, Folder 14)
  - Project 18-South Dakota, 1969-1970; Series 8 (Box 2710, Folder 15)
  - Project 18-South Dakota-Coverage, Correspondence, ca. 1969-1970; Series 8 (Box 2710, Folder 16)
  - Project 18-Span 70, 1971; Series 8 (Box 2710, Folder 17)
  - Project 18-S.J. 7-Status Report-YFC, 1971; Series 8 (Box 2710, Folder 18)
  - Project 18-Status Report-Constitutional Amendment, 1971; Series 8 (Box 2710, Folder 19)
  - Project 18-Speeches, 1969; Series 8 (Box 2710, Folder 20)
  - Project 18-State Correspondence, 1969; Series 8 (Box 2711, Folder 1)
  - Project 18-State-by-State Survey and NEA Mastery in Learning Project, 1985; Series 8 (Box 2711, Folder 2)
  - Project 18-State Referendum, 1971; Series 8 (Box 2711, Folder 3)
  - Project 18-State Referendum Contacts, 1970; Series 8 (Box 2711, Folder 4)
  - Project 18-State Referendum Results, 1970; Series 8 (Box 2711, Folder 5)
  - Project 18-Student National Education Association Association (SNEA) Correspondence To and From States, 1971-1972; Series 8 (Box 2711, Folder 6)
  - Project 18-SNEA Correspondence To and From States, 1971-1972; Series 8 (Box 2711, Folder 7)
  - Project 18-SNEA Correspondence To and From States, 1971-1972; Series 8 (Box 2711, Folder 8)
  - Project 18-SNEA Correspondence To and From States, 1971-1972; Series 8 (Box 2711, Folder 9)
  - Project 18-Student NEA Political Action Committee, 1971; Series 8 (Box 2711, Folder 10)
  - Project 18-Student Policy-NEA, 1970; Series 8 (Box 2711, Folder 11)
  - Project 18-Teach In, 1969-1970; Series 8 (Box 2712, Folder 1)
  - Project 18-Telegrams sent by P-18, P/S, ca. 1970; Series 8 (Box 2712, Folder 2)
  - Project 18-Tennessee, 1968-1970; Series 8 (Box 2712, Folder 3)
  - Project 18-Tennessee-General Vote 18 Correspondence, 1969-1970; Series 8 (Box 2712, Folder 4)
  - Project 18-Tennessee-Wyoming, 1971-1972; Series 8 (Box 2712, Folder 5)
  - Project 18-Testimonies, 1969; Series 8 (Box 2712, Folder 6)
  - Project 18-Testimony-18-year-old Vote, 1969-1970; Series 8 (Box 2712, Folder 7)
  - Project 18-Texas, 1969; Series 8 (Box 2712, Folder 8)
  - Project 18-Texas-Correspondence, 1969-1970; Series 8 (Box 2712, Folder 9)
  - Project 18-U.S. Congressional Profiles, ca. 1970; Series 8 (Box 2712, Folder 10)
  - Project 18-Utah, 1969-1971; Series 8 (Box 2712, Folder 11)
  - Project 18-Utah-General Correspondence, 1969-1970; Series 8 (Box 2712, Folder 12)
  - Project 18-Vermont, 1969; Series 8 (Box 2712, Folder 13)
  - Project 18-Vermont-General Correspondence, 1969; Series 8 (Box 2712, Folder 14)
  - Project 18-Virginia, 1969; Series 8 (Box 2712, Folder 15)
  - Project 18-Virginia-Correspondence, 1971; Series 8 (Box 2712, Folder 16)
  - Project 18-Vote 18 Correspondence Before Project 18, 1968-1969; Series 8 (Box 2712, Folder 17)
  - Project 18-Voting Age (Miscellaneous-Unfoldered Documents), 1970; Series 8 (Box 2713, Folder 1)
  - Project 18-Voting Rights 1970 Summary of Y.F.C. Action, Series 8 (Box 2713, Folder 2)
  - Project 18-V.R.A.-'70-News Releases P-18 and Y.F.C., 1970; Series 8 (Box 2713, Folder 3)
  - Project 18-Washington [1/2], 1969-1971; Series 8 (Box 2713, Folder 4)
  - Project 18-Washington [2/2], 1970; Series 8 (Box 2713, Folder 5)
  - Project 18-Washington (General Vote 18 Correspondence, Referendum & Hand-Out Correspondence, Voter Registration Effort Correspondnece, SPAN Correspondence), 1969-1970; Series 8 (Box 2713, Folder 6)
  - Project 18-West Virginia, 1969-1970; Series 8 (Box 2713, Folder 7)
  - Project 18-White House Conference on Children and Youth, 1970-1971; Series 8 (Box 2713, Folder 8)
  - Project 18-Why NEA Support P/S, 1967-1969; Series 8 (Box 2713, Folder 9)
  - Project 18-Wisconsin, 1969-1970; Series 8 (Box 2713, Folder 10)
  - Project 18-Wisconsin (General Vote 18 Correspondence), 1970; Series 8 (Box 2713, Folder 11)
  - Project 18-Wyoming, 1969-1970; Series 8 (Box 2713, Folder 12)
  - Project 18-Wyoming (General Correspondence, Teach-In, Referendum Night Coverage, Ratification Correspondence), ca. 1969; Series 8 (Box 2713, Folder 13)
  - Project 18-Youth Franchise, 1970-1971; Series 8 (Box 2713, Folder 14)
  - Project 18-Youth Franchise Coalition [1/2], 1968-1969; Series 8 (Box 2713, Folder 15)
  - Project 18-Youth Franchise Coalition [2/2], 1969; Series 8 (Box 2713, Folder 16)
  - Project 18-Y.F.C. 26th Amendment Support, 1971; Series 8 (Box 2713, Folder 17)
  - Project 18-Y.F.C. Advisory Board Formed in View of 18-Year-Old Statute, 1969-1970; Series 8 (Box 2713, Folder 18)
  - Project 18-Y.F.C. Beginning History 18-Year-Old Vote, 1969; Series 8 (Box 2713, Folder 19)
  - Project 18-Y.F.C. Fund-Raising Budget, Series 8 (Box 2714, Folder 1)
  - Project 18-Y.F.C. Fund-Raising Materials 18-Year-Old Vote, 1966-1969; Series 8 (Box 2714, Folder 2)
  - Project 18-Y.F.C. Lawyer's Committee, 1969; Series 8 (Box 2714, Folder 3)
  - Project 18-Y.F.C. Newsletters, 18-Year-Old Vote, 1969; Series 8 (Box 2714, Folder 4)
  - Project 18-Y.F.C. Organizing Papers January 27, 1969, Series 8 (Box 2714, Folder 5)
  - Project 18-Y.F.C. Support V.R.A., 1970; Series 8 (Box 2714, Folder 6)
  - Project 18-Young Republicans, 18-Year-Old Vote-Constitutional Amendment, 1969-1970; Series 8 (Box 2714, Folder 7)
  - Project Dropout-AMPR Audiotapes, 1978; Series 8 (Box 2714, Folder 8)
  - Project Dropout-Asociation de Maestros de Puerto Rico; Asociacion Nacional Para la Educacion, Series 8 (Box 2714, Folder 9)
  - Project Dropout-Automation Project, 1960-1962; Series 8 (Box 2714, Folder 10)
  - Project Dropout-Dropout Proposal to Ford Foundation, 1961-1963; Series 8 (Box 2714, Folder 11)
  - Project Dropout-"Dropout Studies: Design and Conduct", 1965; Series 8 (Box 2715, Folder 1)
  - Project Dropout-Each One, Reach One (flyer with Dr. Carr's letter; Dropout Problem), 1963; Series 8 (Box 2715, Folder 2)
  - Project Dropout-E.I.A., 1962-1963; Series 8 (Box 2715, Folder 3)
  - Project Dropout-Forms-Reports, n.d.; Series 8 (Box 2715, Folder 4)
  - Project Dropout-"Holding Power/Large City School Systems", 1964; Series 8 (Box 2715, Folder 5)
  - Project Dropout-Joint Commission, Correctional Manpower & Training, Correctional Briefings, 1968; Series 8 (Box 2715, Folder 6)
  - Project Dropout-Joint Commission on Correctional Manpower and Training (Correspondence), 1963-1968; Series 8 (Box 2715, Folder 7)
  - Project Dropout-Joint Commission on Correctional Manpower and Training-Minutes, Newsletters, etc., 1964-1969; Series 8 (Box 2716, Folder 1)
  - Project Dropout-Mr. Daniel Schreiber, 1965-1966; Series 8 (Box 2716, Folder 2)
  - Project Dropout-Norton, John Dr., 1961-1962; Series 8 (Box 2716, Folder 3)
    Norton, John K.
  - Project Dropout-Presentation Ceremony, Gov. Terry Sanford-Raleigh, North Carolina, 1964 May 5; Series 8 (Box 2716, Folder 4)
  - Project Dropout-Project on Automation, 1961-1962; Series 8 (Box 2716, Folder 5)
  - Project Dropout-Recommendations-Physical Plant, Academic Needs, Parent-Teachers, Association Role, 1978; Series 8 (Box 2717, Folder 1)
  - Project Dropout-"Report of NEA Special Project on Urban Services"-Norton, John K., Director, 1962 February; Series 8 (Box 2717, Folder 2)
  - Project Dropout-Puerto Rico, 1978-1979; Series 8 (Box 2717, Folder 3)
  - Project Dropout-School Dropouts, 1961-1965; Series 8 (Box 2717, Folder 4)
  - Project Dropout-Special Project on Urban Services-Misc. Unfoldered Material, 1961-1975; Series 8 (Box 2718, Folder 1)
  - Project Dropout-Virgil M. Rogers (Automation Project), 1963-1964; Series 8 (Box 2718, Folder 2)
    Rogers, Virgil M.
  - Project Educational Neglect-Critical Issues Conference Program, 1975 July 3-4; Series 8 (Box 2718, Folder 3)
  - Project Educational Neglect-Report and Working Papers, 1975; Series 8 (Box 2718, Folder 4)
  - Project Educational Neglect-On-Site and Research Reports, 1975; Series 8 (Box 2718, Folder 5)
  - Project Educational Neglect-Misc. Unfoldered Material, 1975 April; Series 8 (Box 2718, Folder 6)
  - Project GAP-Concept Paper, 1972 October; Series 8 (Box 2718, Folder 7)
  - Project Interchange: A Summary Report of the First Two Years, undated; series 8 (Box 4418, Folder 9)
  - Project Interchange Evaluation, January, 1970; Series 8 (Box 4244, Folder 10)
  - Project Interchange Final Report & Updates, 1969-1970; Series 8 (Box 4244, Folder 11)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-Alabama, Alaska, Arizona, Arkansas, 1953; Series 8 (Box 2718, Folder 8)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-Arizona, 1958; Series 8 (Box 2718, Folder 9)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-Auxiliary School Services, ca. 1958; Series 8 (Box 2718, Folder 10)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-Ben Thompson, 1958-1959; Series 8 (Box 2718, Folder 11)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-Bibliography, 1958-1959; Series 8 (Box 2718, Folder 12)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-California [file 1/2], 1957-1959; Series 8 (Box 2718, Folder 13)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-California [file 2/2], 1957-1959; Series 8 (Box 2718, Folder 14)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-California-Los Angeles County Special School, 1957-1959; Series 8 (Box 2719, Folder 1)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-California-San Luis, 1955-1959; Series 8 (Box 2719, Folder 2)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-California-Specials Schools and Youth Authority, 1957-1959; Series 8 (Box 2719, Folder 3)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-California, State of, 1958-1959; Series 8 (Box 2719, Folder 4)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-Colorado, 1958-1959; Series 8 (Box 2719, Folder 5)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-Colorado-Connecticut, 1958-1959; Series 8 (Box 2719, Folder 6)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-Connecticut, 1958-1959; Series 8 (Box 2719, Folder 7)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-Council on American Education-Manuscript on Testing and Evaluation, 1959-1960; Series 8 (Box 2719, Folder 8)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-Council on Instruction (Am. Ed.), 1959; Series 8 (Box 2719, Folder 9)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-Council on Instruction-Staff Person, 1959-1960; Series 8 (Box 2719, Folder 10)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-D.C., 1957-1959; Series 8 (Box 2719, Folder 11)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-DC Commisioner's Youth Council, 1956-1958; Series 8 (Box 2720, Folder 1)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-DC Health Welfare Council-City and Federal Publications, 1958-1959; Series 8 (Box 2720, Folder 2)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-Delaware-DC-Florida, 1958; Series 8 (Box 2720, Folder 3)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-"Delinquent Behavior", 1958-1959; Series 8 (Box 2720, Folder 4)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-"Delinquent Behavior: Implementation of Theory for Prevention and Control", 1959 May 14-15; Series 8 (Box 2720, Folder 5)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-Dr. Kvaraceus-California, 1958; Series 8 (Box 2720, Folder 6)
    Kvaraceus, William Clement
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-Document I-Reactions, etc., 1959; Series 8 (Box 2720, Folder 7)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-Film Project, 1959; Series 8 (Box 2720, Folder 8)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-Florida, 1958; Series 8 (Box 2720, Folder 9)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-Foreword, ca. 1959; Series 8 (Box 2720, Folder 10)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-General Correspondence F-G, 1958-1959; Series 8 (Box 2721, Folder 1)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-Georgia, 1958; Series 8 (Box 2721, Folder 2)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-Group I, ca. 1958; Series 8 (Box 2721, Folder 3)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-Group II, ca. 1958; Series 8 (Box 2721, Folder 4)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-Group III, ca. 1958-1959; Series 8 (Box 2721, Folder 5)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-Group IV, ca. 1958-1959; Series 8 (Box 2721, Folder 6)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-Group V, ca. 1958-1959; Series 8 (Box 2721, Folder 7)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-Group VI, ca. 1958-1959; Series 8 (Box 2721, Folder 8)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-Group VII, ca. 1958-1959; Series 8 (Box 2721, Folder 9)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-Group VIII, ca. 1958-1959; Series 8 (Box 2721, Folder 10)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-Group IX, ca. 1959; Series 8 (Box 2721, Folder 11)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-Group X, ca. 1959; Series 8 (Box 2721, Folder 12)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-Group XI, ca. 1958-1959; Series 8 (Box 2721, Folder 13)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-Group XII, ca. 1958-1959; Series 8 (Box 2721, Folder 14)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-Group XIII, ca. 1958-1959; Series 8 (Box 2721, Folder 15)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-Group XIV, ca. 1958-1959; Series 8 (Box 2721, Folder 16)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-Group XV, ca. 1958-1959; Series 8 (Box 2721, Folder 17)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-Idaho, 1959; Series 8 (Box 2721, Folder 18)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-Identifying the Child Needing Help in the Classroom, ca. 1959; Series 8 (Box 2721, Folder 19)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-Illinois, 1957-1959; Series 8 (Box 2721, Folder 20)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-Individual Reports Read, 1957-1959; Series 8 (Box 2722, Folder 1)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-Illinois, 1957-1958; Series 8 (Box 2721, Folder 21)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-Indiana, 1957-1958; Series 8 (Box 2721, Folder 22)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-Indiv. Quotes and National Invitational Conference, 1958-1959; Series 8 (Box 2721, Folder 23)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-Intro., ca. 1958-1959; Series 8 (Box 2722, Folder 2)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-Iowa, 1958; Series 8 (Box 2722, Folder 3)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-Iowa, 1957-1959; Series 8 (Box 2722, Folder 4)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-"Juvenile Delinquency: Research, Theory, & Comment", 1958; Series 8 (Box 2722, Folder 5)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-Kansas-Kentucky-Louisiana, 1957-1958; Series 8 (Box 2722, Folder 6)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-Kentucky-Louisiana, 1958-1959; Series 8 (Box 2722, Folder 7)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-Legislative Activities, 1959; Series 8 (Box 2722, Folder 8)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-Loose Items in Box [file 1/2], ca. 1959; Series 8 (Box 2722, Folder 9)
    Contains 3 negatives.
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-Loose Items in Box [file 2/2], ca. 1959; Series 8 (Box 2722, Folder 10)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-Los Angeles-County, City, etc., 1957-1959; Series 8 (Box 2722, Folder 11)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-Maine-Maryland-Massachusetts, 1958; Series 8 (Box 2722, Folder 12)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-Massachusetts, 1957-1958; Series 8 (Box 2722, Folder 13)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-May 14-15 Meeting Correspondence, 1959 May 14-15; Series 8 (Box 2722, Folder 14)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-May 14-15 Meeting-Groups-Organization, Chairmen, Records, 1959 May 14-15; Series 8 (Box 2723, Folder 1)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-May 14-15 Meeting-Invitation and Follow-Ups, 1959 May 14-15; Series 8 (Box 2723, Folder 2)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-May 14-15 Meeting-Participants-List, 1959 May 14-15; Series 8 (Box 2723, Folder 3)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-Mayflower Hotel Bills Only, 1959; Series 8 (Box 2723, Folder 4)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-Michigan [file 1/2], 1958-1959; Series 8 (Box 2723, Folder 5)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-Michigan [file 2/2], 1958-1959; Series 8 (Box 2723, Folder 6)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-Michigan-Detroit Only, 1953-1959; Series 8 (Box 2723, Folder 7)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-Minnesota, 1951-1959; Series 8 (Box 2723, Folder 8)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-Minnesota (except St. Paul), 1955-1956; Series 8 (Box 2724, Folder 1)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-Minnesota-St. Paul, 1954-1959; Series 8 (Box 2724, Folder 2)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-Miscellaneous, 1958-1959; Series 8 (Box 2724, Folder 3)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-Mississippi-Missouri, 1958; Series 8 (Box 2724, Folder 4)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-Missouri, 1958; Series 8 (Box 2724, Folder 5)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-Montana-Nebraska-Nevada, 1959; Series 8 (Box 2724, Folder 6)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-National Conference, 1959 May 14-15; Series 8 (Box 2724, Folder 7)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-NEA Non-Participants and Congress Invitees, 1959; Series 8 (Box 2724, Folder 8)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-New Jersey [file 1/2], 1958-1959; Series 8 (Box 2724, Folder 9)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-New Jersey [file 2/2], 1958-1959; Series 8 (Box 2724, Folder 10)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-New Jersey-Youth Study Commission, 1958; Series 8 (Box 2724, Folder 11)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-New Hampshire-New Mexico, 1958-1959; Series 8 (Box 2724, Folder 12)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-New York City, 1955-1959; Series 8 (Box 2724, Folder 13)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-New York-Private, 1958-1959; Series 8 (Box 2725, Folder 1)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-New York State, 1958; Series 8 (Box 2725, Folder 2)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-New York State, 1958-1959; Series 8 (Box 2725, Folder 3)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-News Clippings, 1958-1959; Series 8 (Box 2725, Folder 4)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-North Carolina, 1958; Series 8 (Box 2725, Folder 5)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-North Carolina-North Dakota-Ohio, 1958-1959; Series 8 (Box 2725, Folder 6)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-North Dakota, 1958; Series 8 (Box 2725, Folder 7)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-NYC Board of Education, 1957-1959; Series 8 (Box 2725, Folder 8)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-Ohio, 1959; Series 8 (Box 2725, Folder 9)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-Oklahoma-Oregon-Pennsylvania, 1956-1958; Series 8 (Box 2725, Folder 10)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-Oregon, 1958-1959; Series 8 (Box 2725, Folder 11)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-Parents and Teachers Association, 1958-1959; Series 8 (Box 2725, Folder 12)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-Personal Reactions to Conference, 1959 May-September; Series 8 (Box 2725, Folder 13)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-Program Outline, 1958; Series 8 (Box 2726, Folder 1)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-Providing Help Through Auxiliary Special Services, 1958; Series 8 (Box 2726, Folder 2)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-Providing Help Through Curriculum Adjustment, ca. 1958; Series 8 (Box 2726, Folder 3)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-Providing Help Through Curriculum Adjustments-Final, 1958; Series 8 (Box 2726, Folder 4)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-Providing Help Through Special Classes, ca. 1956; Series 8 (Box 2726, Folder 5)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-Providing Help Within the Classroom, ca. 1957; Series 8 (Box 2726, Folder 6)
  - Project Juvenile Delinquency-Providing Help Within the Classroom, ca. 1957; Series 8 (Box 2726, Folder 7)